[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 10]
Eloping sounds like a TV plot,
but back then,
we really weren't afraid of anything, not even death.
I see.
Dr... Dr. Xie.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I lost my composure just now.
I was moved by your story.
Let's continue.
So,
that memory just now
was when you loved each other the most.
I suppose so.
Let's go back to the beginning.
Your initial question was
how to make the other person fall in love with you again.
After awakening the memories,
we need to find your core conflict.
The one who created the problem must be the one to solve it.
I just don't know
what your biggest unresolved issue is.
You can't sleep?
No, I fell asleep.
I'll go
see if Yu Tu is asleep.
She wants a drink.
You can't sleep?
Yes.
Have a drink?
I'm sorry.
I sprayed it on you again.
I know you too well.
-Why can't you sleep? -Why can't you sleep?
My mind is a mess.
I wish you hadn't
saved me back then.
In Southern Qin,
if you hadn't meddled
and just left me in that courtyard...
So what if I meddled?
I would have saved anyone.
But if I had to do it again,
I wouldn't want it to be anyone else.
Ning Changyue.
Do you dare
to go out and buy me some osmanthus cake?
Just that?
I thought you were going to ask for the moon.
Wait for me.
Then do you dare
to sell all the things
you've collected?
Hello,
Wu Ya.
Uncle.
Sell all the things ...
Hello?
What's up?
Uncle?
Nothing.
You know the little cat we keep at home
is very naughty.
She accidentally pressed the phone.
I'm hanging up.
Do we
have a cat at home?
Any other requests,
Your Highness?
Ning Changyue.
Do you dare to jump off a cliff with me again?
♪ My heart aches as if it's tearing through my chest ♪
♪ Shattered into pieces ♪
♪ Until my lungs have nothing left ♪
♪ I'll kill the beauty that kept me awake ♪
Are you ready?
From now on,
whether in heaven or on earth,
♪ I'll kill the beauty that kept me awake ♪
you and I
will never be apart.
We are still alive.
My leg feels like it's broken.
Is it because of that pill?
Hey, Song Yiqiu.
Are you busy right now?
Why didn't you come looking for me?
I've waited for you for 72 years and 37 days.
Wait for me. Don't rush.
Why didn't you come looking for me?
I really can't die.
Try stabbing me.
It hurts!
What did you mean by raising a cat just now?
Why bother getting a cat?
They might as well raise me.
Go away.
We are not monsters.
Go away!
Oh my God.
Go away.
Song Yiqiu.
Can I come to see you?
Am I crazy?
Do I have a death wish?
How am I supposed to explain this?
There's still time.
Do it now.
Let's take care of business.
What are you doing?
It's not working.
Freeze!
Look at you.
Be careful with my sapling.
Okay.
I have to say,
your trick is quite practical.
Of course.
I can stop time,
control people's minds,
and even erase memories.
Why else do you think
Ning Changyue wanted to learn from me?
Then...
Well...
When did that happen?
Let me think.
I don't remember.
Anyway.
He learned it because of you.
Because of me?
Did you learn from Yu Tu because of me?
Actually, I just wanted to
solve these problems thoroughly.
Maybe then you wouldn't be angry.
Ning Changyue.
Do you dare
to fall in love with me again?
♪ You are my light, my reason why ♪
♪ You shine upon the depths inside ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I finally learned ♪
♪ To keep moving forward ♪
Hello, everyone.
I moved a while ago, remember?
Guess what I found in the old house.
Miss Song, what are you doing?
My grandmother's hidden treasure.
Song Yiqiu,
what are you doing?
A Republic of China-era marriage certificate.
You probably won't find
another one online in this condition.
Come on,
let's take a look at the format first.
Two families joined in marriage.
Bound together in matrimony.
This opening is very classic.
Let's continue reading.
Let me see.
Today, with these words written in red,
our fates are bound by the red cord.
I, Huai, sincerely
forge an eternal bond with you.
Forge an eternal bond with you.
I'll open it for everyone to see now.
May we know each other through every season,
in warmth and cold alike.
May we share in all the joys
that life has to offer.
Let the sun and moon bear witness,
and heaven and earth be our testament.
If I betray your heart,
I betray heaven itself.
My heart shall never waver,
nor shall I ever forsake you.
Lin Huai.
Baiwei,
please marry me.
Sworn by,
Lin Huai.
Song Baiwei.
Song Yiqiu.
Is it you?
Is it really you?
♪ Longing flows on like water ♪
♪ Through the turning nights and days ♪
♪ I gaze upon your light ♪
♪ And stay here, watching over you ♪
♪ Longing carries through the years ♪
♪ As fate turns back around ♪
♪ If I could grow old with you ♪
♪ This life would be enough ♪
Where is he?
Where is Ning Changyue?
He...
I don't know.
Was it because things got awkward
between you two yesterday?
Go do your thing.
Look,
how did two more flowers appear overnight?
Let me see.
Could it be that once the flowers bloom,
the Vow to Live Forever will be broken?
What if you two suddenly
grow old and lose your looks,
while I'm the only one who stays young and beautiful?
Could it be that the shows you've been watching lately
are all about these manipulative girls?
Yeah.
My show,
"The Manipulative Beauty Tames the Crazy Prince",
has updated.
Then I'll get going.
Time to watch my show.
It seems this time,
the eternal life is really going to end.
Mr. Painting,
or Mrs. Painting,
can I ask you a favor?
Regarding the frequency of this blooming,
can we control it to
once a week...
No, no, no.
Once a month.
One flower at a time,
okay?
We need to take a scientific approach
to flowering.
Slow and steady.
Quality
over quantity.
Sound good?
Is it okay?
Please, please, please.
Please, just slow down the blooming.
You...
You, you, you...
I tried to reason with you nicely, but you wouldn't listen, would you?
You're driving me crazy.
That's fine.
I'll bring you out when you've calmed down.
Ning Changyue.
Lin Huai.